DANIEL **KELLY**

403 Pattern House , Castle Street, Stalybridge, SK151AP

danny.kelly@live.com

07561449110

SUMMARY

Experienced site manager professional with strong leadership and relationship-building skills. Currently working freelance site manager fit out .am highly motivated and consistent in turning out contracts on time and defect free. Always committed, organised ambitious and service driven.

EXPERIENCE

2016 to current Freelance site manager worked for various companys ISG, SPIE,SHAYLORS,AC

electrical and interiors. Student accommodation. Banking frameworks.

04/2008 to 2016

Site Manager

Morris and Spottiswood - Warrington, Lancashire

I joined the business in April 2008 employed as a roofer/supervisor, working under the maintenance division covering NHBC works, i have since been promoted to site manager working under fit out division covering national banking frameworks. My role includes all aspects day to day site management, from pre start meetings to absolute completion. Working on frameworks has been testing at times i have recently completed a primary contract on Canary wharf which involved arranging permits and planning consent from landlords, this work completed on time and was rewarding once complete.

My employment qualification's Include- SMSTS 5 day, SSSTS 2 day, CSCS Ukata Asbestos awareness, St JOHN 1st aider, fire warden, Pasma, Ipaf, NVQ 3 Roofing slating/tiling, advanced working at heights, Scaffold inspection.

List of completed programs / values -

Natwest Buxton modular refurb 4 week duration 300k

Natwest Washwood Heath modular refurb 4 week duration 300k

RBS Preston re-fresh 3 week duration 150k

RBS Bradford re-fresh 3 week duration 150k

Natwest Pickering modular refurb 4 week duration 300k

Natwest Pontefract modular 3 week duration 400k

Natwest Leeds Flagship 10 week flagship 600k Natwest Canary Wharf primary 8 week 500k

RBS Castle Douglas modular 4 week 300k

RBS Dumbarton modular 4 week 300k

Natwest Hanley Primary 8 week 500k

I also have experience covering contracts with Marks and Spencers,

CO-OP, Superdrugs, Nhbc.

02/1999 to 04/2008

Roofer / working supervisor

KMR Taylor and Sons Itd - Bolton, Lancashire

Served a three year apprenticeship studying roof Slating and Tiling achieved NVQ level 3 and moved up to become site supervisor, I have had experience with working on listed building such as churches/ town halls to working on housing association property where its fast turn around and budgets are tight.

EDUCATION

2003 NVQ Level 3: Roofing/slating & tiling

Bolton six form collage - Bolton

1999 High School Diploma

St THOMAS MORE RC - Denton

 $Maths, English, Science\ x\ 3, Geography, Sociology, French, I.T.$

All studied to GCSE grade A-C

References given **REFERENCES**

on request.